{
  "question": "How do you react to danger?",
  "options": [
    {
      "answer": "I don't mind charging in.",
      "question": "Are you more strong or nimble?",
      "options": [
        {
          "answer": "Strong",
          "question": "Are you good with the gods?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "I got 'em on speed dial.",
              "question": "I live my faith by...",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Channeling the nature and power of my god",
                  "class": "cleric"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Delivering righteous justice",
                  "class": "paladin"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Meh.",
              "question": "Are you prone to fly into a rage?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "No more than the next adventurer",
                  "question": "How cool would it be to turn into a bear?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "So cool!",
                      "class": "druid"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "I have allergies.",
                      "class": "fighter"
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Raaaaaahhhhrrr!!!",
                  "class": "barbarian"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "Nimble",
          "question": "Do you live for kung-fu movies?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "Bruce Lee is my idol.",
              "class": "monk"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Not so much.",
              "question": "Would you risk your life for a good story?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "I think not.",
                  "question": "I am deadly because...",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "I'm a master hunter.",
                      "class": "ranger"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "I'm a born schemer.",
                      "question": "My schemes usually involve...",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Cloak and dagger tactics.",
                          "class": "rogue"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Allying myself with dark and strange elements.",
                          "class": "warlock"
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "I'm experienced in the art of combat.",
                      "class": "fighter"
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "You know it!",
                  "class": "bard"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "I deal with it from a safe distance.",
      "question": "What do you rely on most?",
      "options": [
        {
          "answer": "Skills",
          "question": "How good are you at being quiet?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "*silence*",
              "question": "Do you keep any pets?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "My best friends are ferocious beasts.",
                  "class": "ranger"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "What, like a gerbil?",
                  "question": "I'm trained to kill using...",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "My brain. And maybe poison.",
                      "class": "rogue"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Anything that skewers, slices, or smashes.",
                      "class": "fighter"
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "I don't know, i've never tried it!",
              "class": "bard"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "Magic",
          "question": "I want...",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "Magical stamina for days",
              "class": "warlock"
            },
            {
              "answer": "One or two supernatural nukes",
              "class": "sorcerer"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Flexibility",
              "question": "Are you the academic type?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Not necessarily",
                  "question": "Are you religious?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "No, my power comes from my righteous lute solos.",
                      "class": "bard"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "No, my power comes from within.",
                      "class": "sorcerer"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Define \"religious.\"",
                      "question": "Where does your power come from?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "My connection with nature",
                          "class": "druid"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "A creepy, otherworldy pact",
                          "class": "warlock"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "The gods",
                          "class": "cleric"
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "I'm a bookworm.",
                  "class": "wizard"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}